Porn games, Sex chat
====================

& 674 sex positions  
AChat
---------------------------

### Login

 Username: 

Password: 

[Home page](https://www.funnyadultgamesplay.com/) > [Privacy policy](https://www.funnyadultgamesplay.com/privacy-policy/)

Privacy policy
--------------

#### By using this site or the AChat Client Software, you signify your agreement to this Privacy policy.

ACHAT'S AND FUNNYADULTGAMESPLAY.COM'S PRIVACY POLICY The AChat and www.funnyadultgamesplay.com privacy policy has been provided with intent to inform our users (users and members) about the process of data collection, storage, distribution and safety process we employ at www.funnyadultgamesplay.com ("Website") and the AChat Client Software ("Product"). By using the Website or Product, you agree to our privacy and security policy and terms of contract. The term using includes but is not limited to visiting, registering and accessing the contents of Website and Product. We maintain that all the measures taken to protect your data are completely lawful. We reserve the right to amend or change the contents of the privacy policy without any advance notice. Thus, it is recommended that you keep checking the policy page regularly. At our Website and Product, the privacy of our customers is of utmost importance for us and we respect the concerns regarding the same. We want to assure you that your information and data is safe with us. We employ highest standard of physical and electronic measures to protect the safety, security and secrecy of your personal information. In order to create an environment of better understanding between the user, and us we are hereby declaring the modes of data collection, storage, and distribution related to you (the user). COLLECTION OF INFORMATION AND DATA - USER SUPPLIED INFORMATION During registration, we require the user to provide us with following information. - You are eighteen (18) EIGHTEEN years of age or older - (Email address - optional) CONFIDENTIALITY We STRONGLY maintain that we do not distribute your personally identifiable data with any third party without your prior consent. We DO NOT sell your information to anyone whatsoever. We ensure complete secrecy and privacy of your data entrusted to us. Provided, nothing in this clause shall stop us from disclosing any information to law enforcement agencies when a legally sustainable request is received or when the disclosure is necessary for public health and well being. We might provide your information to the third party payment gateways in order to confirm your payment and ensure that you get respective services from us. We may use your information to make further contracts and agreements in course of delivery of our services. We maintain that we reserve the right to distribute your information with our sister companies within our business group without any prior consent or information. We may also use such information to make your experience with our Website better. We may also use your information in absolutely statistical format for internal research and related market purposes. We will use your email address to send our offers, newsletters, advertisement details etc. You can always decide to opt out of the same by sending a request via Website's Support Form. We will honor your concerns immediately. PROFILE INFORMATION We allow our users to create profiles on our website. We request our users to conduct themselves in highest standard of personal behavior and do not post any defamatory or inflammatory content on our website. We out rightly discourage any publication of information publically on your profile that may prove harmful to you, any other person, organization etc or whose publication has been adjudged illegal by a competent court. We maintain that we shall not be liable for any user posted public information including testimonials that give rise to a legal dispute, damage or loss. An dispute related to any information posted by users in their profile or in public domain within the website shall be brought to our notice by sending a complaint at Website's Support Form. We will take appropriate measures regarding the same. PUBLICATION BY WEBSITE AND PRODUCT We maintain that all the information we publish on our website or in the Product is in accordance with law and no personally identifiable data is published without prior consent of the users. We may reproduce some of the contents posted by the users in good faith and we shall not be liable for any loss or damage due to the same. AUTOMATIC COLLECTION OF INFORMATION THROUGH COOKIES and other related mechanisms We accept that we collect certain information about the user through cookies and other related mechanisms. The information is purely technical in nature. The collection of the information is necessary for: To obtain statistics and usage data To improve Website, Product experience and make it more personalized. We assure you that none of the information collected under this category are personally identifiable in nature. The data does not identify you personally through your name, contact, address or any other related information. We maintain the right to use such information for market strategies, business research and internal surveys. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES Our Website may contain certain third party links. These third party links do not belong to us and thus, we do not assume any liability for any loss or dispute arising out of the information entrusted to them by you. We also reserve the right to promote our Website, Product and related content through other websites. These websites may or may not collect anonymous information about you. We shall not be held liable for any breach of loss of data arising out of the same. We do not share any personally identifiable data with these third party websites. CONSENT We will not sell your personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission. USE OF DEMOGRAPHIC/ PROFILE DATA/ YOUR INFORMATION   We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our services, inform you about our offers, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on the Website and in the Product. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer the Website and the Product. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. EXCEPTION TO NON-DISCLOSURE AND PRIVACY OF DATA WE MAINTAIN THAT we employ all the information collected from you, be it personally identifiable or not, for lawful purposes and to make Website and Product experience better for you. We reserve the right to disclose any of it and all of it if: - We believe that such disclosure is necessary for enforcement of law, court order, police warrant etc. - When such disclosure is essential for maintenance of public health and order. - When such disclosure is essential to restore legal rights of a fellow user. - When we believe in good faith that our Website or Product is being used in order to commit a crime or civil wrong. - When your actions on the Website or in the Product are in contravention of our privacy policy, terms of use or such disclosure is crucial to enforcement of Website's rights. MERGER AND ACQUISITIONS In case of a merger or acquisition, we reserve the right to transfer all the information, including personally identifiable information, stored with the Website or the Product to the new entity or company thus formed. SECURITY POLICY We maintain that security and safety of your data and personal information is of utmost importance to us. We have employed highest possible standard of security measures for the same. We also assure you that all the payment procedures and gateways supported and employed by our website are certified by concerned authorities as secure and safe. Though we assure you that we have employed adequate physical and highly sophisticated technological methods to secure your data, we cannot guarantee you of absolute data safety. While we will take every reasonable step in protection of your data, we shall not be held liable for unauthorized and unlawful act of third parties that are alien to our control. We shall not be responsible for any unavoidable technical or physical glitch and for acts that are beyond human control. BREACH OF PRIVACY POLICY We reserve the right to terminate or suspend any account or delete certain contents from any profile or public domain within the ambit of the Website or the Product if the said account or content is found to be in violation of our privacy policy. We sincerely request you to respect privacy and secrecy concerns of others. The jurisdiction of any breach or dispute shall be determined in accordance with terms of use. CONTACT US In case you have any issue with any of the clauses of this privacy policy, or in case there is a dispute regarding any privacy related matter, contact us via Website's Support Form.

All contents © 2024

#### Porn games, Sex chat - AChat

**Funnyadultgamesplay.com**  
The Official AChat Website.
